<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RentACar</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">2249887752002229</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">NotesGenie</string>
    <!--<string name="server_client_id">560383456095-95icjhcl7jbti4kf04d9ftmt7b6lcapc.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>-->
    <string name="server_client_id">560383456095-6ai1epk3ja55k4fevsmojpouiror8lcq.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Logout</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash">splashActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="head_quarter_base_address">5050 Quorum Drive Suite 700</string>
    <string name="head_quarter_extend_address">Dallas, TX 75254</string>
    <string name="head_quarter_email_address">CramFrenzy.com</string>
    <string name="head_quarter_toll_address">&#160;TOLL &#160;&#160;# +1-888-764-0100</string>
    <string name="head_quarter_fax_address"># +1-(496)-250-6600</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <!--<string name="google_api_key_for_login">AIzaSyDfFecRtRrRxtj4LoqKpF25lmCKgX6ag28</string>-->

    <!--pdf download-->
    <string name="some_error_occurred">Some error occurred</string>
    <string name="start">start</string>
    <string name="completed">completed</string>
    <string name="pause">pause</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="resume">resume</string>
    <string name="restart">restart</string>

    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="permission_not_enabled">Please enable the Write External Storage Permission</string>
    <string name="delete_files">Delete Downloads test files from the file system and try again.</string>
    <string name="delete_title">Are you sure you want to delete %1$s?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="view">VIEW</string>
    <string name="wifiOnly">WiFi Only</string>
    <string name="retry">RETRY</string>
    <string name="complete_over">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="start_fetching">Click start to start fetching game files.</string>
    <string name="fetch_started">Fetching Game Files…</string>
    <string name="fetch_done">Fetching done.</string>
    <string name="fetch_failed">An error occurred whiles fetching the game files.</string>
    <string name="reset">RESET</string>
    <string name="single_download_demo">Single Download Demo</string>
    <string name="download_list_demo">Download List Demo</string>
    <string name="game_file_download_demo">Game File Download Demo</string>
    <string name="percent_progress">%1$d%%</string>
    <string name="downloading">downloading…</string>
    <string name="queued">QUEUED</string>
    <string name="added">ADDED</string>
    <string name="status_unknown">Status Unknown</string>
    <string name="delete_all_files">Delete Downloaded Files</string>
    <string name="file_server">FETCH FILE SERVER DEMO</string>
    <string name="downloaded_files_deleted">Downloads Files Deleted</string>
    <string name="game_download_error">An error occurred, could not get game files.</string>
    <string name="failed_multi_enqueue">Failed Multi Enqueue Demo</string>
    <string name="multi_fragment">MULTI FRAGMENT DEMO</string>
    <string name="enqueue_error">Could not enqueue this request. Check logcat.</string>
    <string name="download_eta_sec">%1$ds left</string>
    <string name="download_eta_min">%1$dm %2$ds left</string>
    <string name="download_eta_hrs">%1$dh %2$dm %3$ds left</string>
    <string name="download_speed_bytes">%1$d B/s</string>
    <string name="download_speed_kb">%1$s KB/s</string>
    <string name="download_speed_mb">%1$s MB/s</string>


    <!--Privay Policy-->


    <string name="privacy_intro">CramFrenzy. (\"CramFrenzy\") recognizes that its visitors, members, users, and others
        who use the website at www.CramFrenzy.com (the \"CramFrenzy Website\") or who access, view or use CramFrenzy
        content or services through emails, RSS feeds, third party advertisements, social networking sites, wnamegets,
        personal feeds, and mobile applications (collectively, the CramFrenzy Website and all such access methods are
        referred to as the \"CramFrenzy Service\") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy provnamees important
        information about the use and disclosure of user information (\"Information\") collected on the CramFrenzy
        Service. CramFrenzy provnamees this Privacy Policy to help you understand what Information CramFrenzy collects
        and how that Information will be used. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that
        CramFrenzy does not own or control or to people that CramFrenzy does not employ or manage.
        This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the CramFrenzy Terms of Use. Your use of the
        CramFrenzy Service and any Information you provnamee on the CramFrenzy Service remains subject to the terms of
        this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at www.CramFrenzy.com.
        By participating, using or viewing the CramFrenzy Service or any content thereof you are accepting the practices
        described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of these terms, then please do not use the
        CramFrenzy Service or its content. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy at
        any time without prior notice. Your continued use of the CramFrenzy Service following the posting of changes to
        these terms means that you accept those changes.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_info_collected">When a student registers on our site he is only asked to give his name and
        email. Afterwards for transfer of money he is to provnamee his credit card information. It is mandatory for the
        instructor to provnamee name, email and credit card information for money transactions.Information Collected
        Upon Registration: If you desire to have access to certain sections of the CramFrenzy Service, you will be
        required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally nameentifiable information to CramFrenzy.
        This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the CramFrenzy Service, login to CramFrenzy
        via Facebook, or if you desire to receive certain communications, updates, and information. Personally
        nameentifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your full name, photos, email
        address, university attended, university major, expected graduation year and term, education history, gender,
        friends, geographic location and other Information that you decnamee to provnamee us with, or that you decnamee
        to include in your account profile. If you register with, or login to, the CramFrenzy Service through Facebook
        (or through any other third-party authentication system), you consent to the transfer of all your personal
        Information from such system to CramFrenzy and CramFrenzy retention and use of such Information pursuant to this
        Privacy Policy.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_additional_info">Once you have registered with the CramFrenzy Service, you may provnamee
        CramFrenzy with a variety of additional personal and non-personal information through your use of the CramFrenzy
        Service, including but not limited to your class schedule, university instructors, grades, textbooks, student
        loans, reviews, ratings, comments, social network profile nameentifier social network contacts and friends,
        career objectives, etc. Provnameing additional Information beyond what is required or collected at registration
        is entirely optional. If you contact us by phone, mail, email, instant message or through any other means, we
        may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_cookies">Use of \"Cookies\" is standard in the Internet industry. Cookies are small text files
        containing a string of alphanumeric characters that are sent to your computer that uniquely nameentify your
        browser. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving passwords and preferences while you\'re at a website. When
        you use the CramFrenzy Service, we may send one or more cookies to your computer. Some cookies are temporary
        (\"session cookies\") and will disappear after you close your browser, but others will stay on your computer
        (\"persistent cookies\" or \"Flash cookies\"). CramFrenzy may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to
        better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and
        web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. Some of our advertisers and business
        partners may serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by third parties. If you wish
        to remove persistent cookies from your hard drive, follow your web browser help file directions. You can also
        reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_traffic_data">When you use the CramFrenzy Service, our servers automatically log certain
        information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. This information may include information
        such as your Internet Protocol (\"IP\") address, computer, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages
        and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those
        pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, related software and
        settings you are using, any search terms you have entered on the CramFrenzy Services or a referral site, and
        other web usage activity.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_usage_pattern">CramFrenzy tracks usage patterns and collects other information about your use
        of the CramFrenzy Service. We may employ various tracking technology including \"clear GIFs\" (a.k.a. Web
        Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users, and clear GIFs in HTML-based emails
        sent to you to track which emails are opened by recipients. CramFrenzy may also contract with third parties to
        track online usage patterns on elements of the CramFrenzy Service.
    </string>


    <string name="priavcy_share_info">We may share Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies or
        for particular purposes including, without limitation, the purposes described below. In all cases, you may
        opt-out of sharing your Information with third parties. Please see \"Offering You Choices - Opt-Out Procedure\"
        below.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_provnameers">We engage certain third parties to perform functions and provnamee services to
        us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance customer relationship, database storage and
        management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Information, including your
        personally-nameentifiable information with these third parties.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_products">If you submit a request for a product or service on the CramFrenzy Service, we will
        share Information about you with our business partners to process and fulfill your request. Our business
        partners may contact you by telephone (including, by autodialer, where applicable), email, on Facebook, via text
        message, or postal mail, based on the Information you provnameed to us, even if you have opted into the National
        Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do
        Not Call List of a specific company. If one of our business partners contacts you and you wish not to be
        contacted again by that business partner with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a
        request to that partner not to contact you again.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_compliance_law">CramFrenzy cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private
        parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any Information about you to government or law
        enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to
        enforce our Terms of Use, protect the security or integrity of the CramFrenzy Service, take precautions to
        avoname liability, investigate and defend against any third-party claims, respond to claims or legal process
        (including court orders, subpoenas and search warrants), protect the property and rights of CramFrenzy or a
        third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally
        actionable activity, or to comply with the law.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_advertising">In addition to ads that we serve you directly, we use third-party advertising
        companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. Both we and our advertising companies use information about
        your visits to this website and other sites you may visit to serve ads to you. In the course of serving
        advertisements to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we
        and our advertising companies may use Web beacons to help manage our online advertising. These Web beacons
        enable us and our third-party ad serving companies to recognize a browser\'s cookie when a browser visits this
        site and to learn which banner ads bring users to our website and to serve you ads that you may find of interest
        elsewhere on the internet. Both CramFrenzy and these companies may use information about your visits to these
        sites and other websites in order to provnamee advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
        CramFrenzy may provnamee Information about you, including personally-nameentifiable information, to assist these
        third parties to personalize the advertising content you see. Further, please note that if you respond to any
        advertisements, the advertiser or ad server may collect certain Information about you and, by responding, you
        are consenting to the possibility that the advertisers will make the assumption that you meet the targeting
        criteria used to display the ad. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad
        servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain
        practices. CramFrenzy Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other
        advertisers or websites.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_usage_info">We may share Information (such as traffic information and usage tracking
        information) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain
        content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the CramFrenzy Service. We may also share
        order information with third parties and business partners.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_subcompanies">We may share Information about you with our subsnameiaries, sister companies,
        parent company, successors, and assigns.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_nonaffiliated">From time to time, we may sell or share your Information, including your
        personally-nameentifiable Information, to non-affiliated third parties and organizations, including without
        limitation your college or university, other public and private institutions, and commercial entities. For
        example, we may share your Information with another company that will use your Information to market to you, or
        to provnamee to you, a product or service that we feel may be of interest to you. We may also sell your
        Information to a business partner that will use your Information for their own marketing purposes.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_offer">You have choices when it comes to protecting your Information. If you do not wish us to
        share your Information with third parties, please send us an e-mail at contact@CramFrenzy.com.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_access_profile">If you are a registered user of the CramFrenzy Service, you may access and
        update or correct the information you provnameed to us by updating your account information or emailing us at
        CramFrenzy.com. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your nameentity before
        granting you access, or making modifications, to your profile. It is your responsibility to maintain the
        accuracy of your account information at all times.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_data_security">CramFrenzy uses commercially reasonable safeguards (physical, managerial, and
        technical) to preserve the integrity and security of your Information. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the
        security of any Information you transmit to CramFrenzy and you transmit any such Information at your own risk.
        Once we receive your transmission of Information, CramFrenzy makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the
        security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such Information may not be
        accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial
        safeguards.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_links_to_other">The CramFrenzy Service may contain links to other websites. The fact that we
        link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third
        party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or
        other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Information from you. Other sites follow different rules
        regarding the use or disclosure of the Information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy
        policies or statements of the other websites you visit.
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_children">CramFrenzy seeks to protect the privacy of young children. For that reason,
        CramFrenzy does not knowingly collect (or maintain) personally nameentifiable information or
        non-personally-nameentifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is
        directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the CramFrenzy
        Service at any time or in any manner. If CramFrenzy learns that personally nameentifiable information of persons
        under 13 years of age has been collected on the CramFrenzy Service without verified parental consent, then
        CramFrenzy will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If a parent or guardian becomes aware
        that his or her child has provnameed us with personally nameentifiable information without their consent, he or
        she should contact us at contact@CramFrenzy.com.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_international_user">The CramFrenzy Service is hosted in the United States. If you are a User
        accessing the CramFrenzy Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations
        governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised
        that through your continued use of the CramFrenzy Service, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy,
        and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your Information to the United States and you consent to that
        transfer.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_bankruptcy">In the event that CramFrenzy is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity,
        we reserve the right, to transfer or assign the Information we have collected from you as part of such merger,
        acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency,
        reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or
        equitable principles affecting creditors\' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal
        Information is treated, transferred, or used.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_changes">This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time and this will be reflected by
        the \"last modified\" date above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of
        the CramFrenzy Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.
    </string>


    <!--Terms of Use-->
    <string name="terms_heading">Welcome to CramFrenzy, a platform to enhance social learning on college campuses. The
        CramFrenzy service and network (collectively, \"the CramFrenzy Service\") are operated by CramFrenzy. a Dallas
        Texas corporation (collectively, \"us\", \"we\" or \"the Company\"). This Terms of Use Agreement (\"Terms of
        Use\" or this \"Agreement\") sets forth the legally binding terms for your use of the CramFrenzy Service. By
        using the CramFrenzy Service, you agree to be bound by this Agreement, whether you are a \"Visitor\" (which
        means that you simply browse the CramFrenzy Service) or you are a \"Member\" (which means that you have logged
        into the CramFrenzy Service, whether through Facebook or some other means). The term \"User\" refers to a
        Visitor or a Member.We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or delete portions of
        these Terms of Use at any time without further notice. If we do this, we will post the changes to these Terms of
        Use on this page and will indicate at the top of this page the Terms of Use\'s effective date. Your continued
        use of the CramFrenzy Service after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the additional Terms of Use.
        If you do not agree to abide by these or any future Terms of Use, please do not use or access the CramFrenzy
        Service. It is your responsibility to regularly review these Terms of Use.
    </string>


    <string name="terms_obligation">To use the CramFrenzy Service, you agree to: (a) provide to us, either directly or
        through the Facebook login system, true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted
        by the CramFrenzy Service registration and login process (such information being the Registration Data) and (b)
        maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. By using the
        CramFrenzy Service, you represent and warrant that (a) you are 14 years of age or older; and (b) your use of the
        CramFrenzy Service does not violate any applicable law or regulation. Registration Data and other information
        about you are subject to our Privacy Policy - for more information, see our full Privacy Policy.
    </string>


    <string name="terms_user_account">You will create an account during the CramFrenzy Service registration process. You
        are responsible for maintaining your account, and you are solely responsible for all activities that occur under
        your account. You agree to (a) immediately notify CramFrenzy of any \"unauthorized\" use of your account or any
        other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. CramFrenzy
        will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with the provisions of this
        paragraph. You agree not to use the account of another Member at any time.
    </string>

    <string name="terms_non_commercial_use">The CramFrenzy Service is provided for your personal and academic use only
        and may not be used about any commercial endeavors except those that are specifically endorsed or approved in
        advance by CramFrenzy. Commercial advertisements, affiliate links, and other forms of solicitation may be
        removed from Member profiles without notice and may result in termination of Membership privileges. Use of the
        CramFrenzy Service, or of any data or information accessed or provided through the CramFrenzy Service, for any
        commercial purpose, or by any commercial entity, is expressly prohibited.You agree not to use or launch any
        automated system or scripts, including without limitation, \"robots,\"; \"spiders,\" \"offline readers,\" etc.,
        to accesses the CramFrenzy Service or to \"scrape,\" \"harvest,\" or otherwise retrieve, any data, documents,
        content or other information from the CramFrenzy Service. You further agree not to collect or harvest any
        personally identifiable information, including account names or email addresses of Members, from the CramFrenzy
        Service, nor to use the communication systems provided by the CramFrenzy Service for any commercial solicitation
        purposes. You agree not to solicit any users of the CramFrenzy Service with respect to their Member profiles or
        Content. Notwithstanding the foregoing, CramFrenzy grants the operators of public search engines permission to
        use spiders to copy materials from the site for the sole purpose of creating publicly available searchable
        indices of the materials. CramFrenzy reserves the right to revoke rights granted herein either generally or in
        specific cases.

        Appropriate legal action will be taken for any illegal or unauthorized use of the CramFrenzy Service (including
        illegal or unauthorized use of any data or information accessed or provided through the CramFrenzy Service).
    </string>

    <string name="terms_fees">You acknowledge that CramFrenzy reserves the right to charge for the CramFrenzy Service
        and to change its fees from time to time in its discretion. If CramFrenzy terminates your Membership because you
        have breached the Agreement, you shall not be entitled to the refund of any unused portion of subscription fees.
    </string>


    <string name="terms_member">You agree that you may not use the CramFrenzy Service in any unlawful manner or in any
        other manner that could damage, disable, overburden or impair the CramFrenzy Service. In addition, you agree not
        to use the CramFrenzy Service to:\n \n
        &#9830; Upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available any content that we deem to be harmful,
        threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, pornographic, libelous, invasive of
        another\'s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;\n \n
        &#9830; Impersonate any person or entity, including but not limited to, a CramFrenzy official, create a false
        identity, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent yourself or your affiliation with any person or entity;\n
        \n
        &#9830; Upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising,
        promotional materials, \"junk mail,\" \"spam,\" \"chain letters,\" \"pyramid schemes,\" or any other form of
        solicitation;\n \n
        &#9830; Upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available any material that contains software viruses or
        any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any
        computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;\n \n
        &#9830; Intimidate, stalk or harass another;\n \n
        &#9830; Harm minors in any way;\n\n
        &#9830; Use or attempt to use another\'s account, service or system without authorization from the Company;\n\n
        &#9830; Forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers to disguise the origin of any information transmitted
        through the CramFrenzy Service;\n\n
        &#9830; Upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available any Content that you do not have a right to
        make available under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information,
        proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under
        nondisclosure agreements).\n\n


    </string>


    <string name="terms_content_posted">You are solely responsible for the media, files, electronic documents, photos,
        profiles, questions, answers, comments, ratings, reviews, descriptions and other content that you create,
        publish or display (hereinafter, \"post") on or through the CramFrenzy Service, or transmit to other Members
        (collectively the \"Content\"). CramFrenzy does not endorse and has no control over the Content. Content is not
        necessarily reviewed by CramFrenzy prior to posting and does not necessarily reflect the opinions or policies of
        CramFrenzy.CramFrenzy reserves the right to reject, refuse to post, or remove any Content at any time, without
        prior notice, in its sole discretion, and for any purpose, including but not limited to, for violations of these
        Terms of Use. CramFrenzy assumes no responsibility for monitoring the CramFrenzy Service for inappropriate
        Content or conduct. If at any time CramFrenzy chooses, in its sole discretion, to monitor the CramFrenzy
        Service, CramFrenzy nonetheless assumes no responsibility for the Content, no obligation to modify or remove any
        inappropriate Content, and no responsibility for the conduct of the User submitting any such Content.By posting
        Content to any part of the CramFrenzy Service, you automatically grant to the Company an irrevocable, perpetual,
        non-exclusive, transferable, fully-paid, royalty-free, worldwide license to use, modify, copy, perform, display,
        reformat, translate, excerpt (in whole or in part) and distribute such information and content and to prepare
        derivative works of, or incorporate into other works, such information and content, and to grant and authorize
        sublicenses of the foregoing. You understand that, under the foregoing license grant, CramFrenzy and its
        sublicensees may make commercial use of your Content in whatever manner it or they deem appropriate, and you
        shall not be entitled to receive any fee, royalty, payment, compensation or remuneration of any kind about such
        commercial use by CramFrenzy and/or its sublicensees.By posting Content to any part of the CramFrenzy Service,
        you represent and warrant that: (i) you own the Content posted by you on or through the CramFrenzy Service or
        otherwise have the right to grant the license set forth in the preceding paragraph, and (ii) the posting of your
        Content on or through the CramFrenzy Service does not violate the privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights,
        contract rights or any other rights of any person, or contain libelous, defamatory or otherwise unlawful
        material. You agree to pay for all royalties, fees, and any other monies owing any person because of any Content
        posted by you to or through the CramFrenzy Service.You understand that by using the CramFrenzy Service, you may
        be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable, and you agree to waive, and hereby do waive,
        any legal or equitable rights or remedies you have or may have against CramFrenzy with respect thereto, and
        agree to indemnify and hold CramFrenzy, its owners/operators, affiliates, and/or licensors, harmless fully
        allowed by law regarding all matters related to your use of the CramFrenzy Service.Under no circumstances will
        CramFrenzy be liable in any way for any Content, including, but not limited to, any errors or omissions in any
        Content, or any loss or damage of any kind incurred because of the use of any Content posted, emailed,
        transmitted or otherwise made available via the CramFrenzy Service. CramFrenzy makes no warranties, express or
        implied, as to the Content or to the accuracy and reliability of the Content or any material or information that
        you transmit to other Members.You acknowledge and agree that CramFrenzy may preserve Content and may also
        disclose Content if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is
        reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with legal process; (b) enforce the Terms of Use; (2) respond to claims that
        any Content violates the rights of third parties; or (3) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of
        CramFrenzy, its Users and/or the public. You understand that the technical processing and transmission of the
        CramFrenzy Service, including your Content, may involve (1) transmissions over various networks; and (2) changes
        to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices.
    </string>


    <string name="terms_proprietary_right">Except for (a) Content posted by you or (b) intellectual property belonging
        to you, all content on the CramFrenzy Service, including but not limited to design, text, graphics, academic
        data, course materials, documents, messages, ratings, reviews, other files, and their selection and arrangement
        (collectively, \"CramFrenzy Content\") are the proprietary property of the Company or its licensors, with all
        rights reserved. You acknowledge and agree that the CramFrenzy Content is protected by copyrights, trademarks,
        service marks, patents or other proprietary rights and laws, including laws covering data access and data
        compilations. No CramFrenzy Content may be modified, copied, distributed, framed, reproduced, republished,
        downloaded, displayed, incorporated into any derivative works or compilations, posted, transmitted, rented or
        sold in any form or by any means, in whole or in part, without the Company\'s prior written permission. You may
        not republish CramFrenzy Content on any Internet, Intranet or Extranet site or incorporate the information in
        any other database or compilation. You agree not to circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security
        related features of the CramFrenzy Service or features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any CramFrenzy
        Content or enforce limitations on use of the CramFrenzy Service or the CramFrenzy Content therein. You agree not
        to access the CramFrenzy Service by any means other than through the interface that is provided by CramFrenzy
        for use in accessing the CramFrenzy Service. You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell or resell, any
        portion of the CramFrenzy Service, use of the CramFrenzy Service, or access to the CramFrenzy Service, other
        than as provided within the scope of the CramFrenzy Service and as expressly permitted under these Terms of Use.
    </string>


    <string name="terms_terminations">CramFrenzy, in its sole discretion and without prior notice, may terminate your
        account (or any part thereof) or use of the CramFrenzy Service, and remove and discard any of your information,
        data and files in your account within the CramFrenzy Service, for any reason, including, without limitation, for
        lack of use, or if CramFrenzy believes that you have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit
        of the Terms of Use. CramFrenzy may also in its sole discretion and at any time modify or discontinue providing
        the CramFrenzy Service, or any part thereof, with or without notice. You agree that CramFrenzy shall not be
        liable to you or any third-party for any termination of your access to the CramFrenzy Service.
    </string>


    <!--cramfrenzy hints-->

    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="min_offer">Automatically decline offers lower than</string>
    <string name="max_offer">Automatically accept offers of at least</string>
    <!--Navigation Headers-->
    <string name="cramFrenzy">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">CramFrenzy</font>
    </string>
    <string name="myAccount">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">My Account</font>
    </string>
    <string name="tutor">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">Tutor</font>
    </string>
    <string name="courses">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">Courses</font>
    </string>
    <string name="books">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">Books</font>
    </string>
    <string name="notes">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">Notes</font>
    </string>
    <string name="flashcards">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">Flash Cards</font>
    </string>
    <string name="myLibrary">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">My Library</font>
    </string>
    <string name="aboutCramfrenzy">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">About CramFrenzy</font>
    </string>


</resources>
